Welcome to the schools on Jawa do you.
I am trying to cover them and I have more than 15 years of experience developing designing and architecting
job applications.
I have interviewed more than 500 candidate during my period or two of the school is to refresh your
job our concepts and fill the gaps in your preparation for job interview.
Remember this is not a job one or one course you are expected to have a programming experience and use
the skills as a quick refresher.
We cover a wide range of topics during this course.
We talk about job black phone Jerry GBM platform independent.
We talk about object oriented programming abstraction and get lation inheritance polymorphism.
We talk about abstract class interfaces.
Cohesion.
And we also discuss collections genitor extract.
Exception handling and we in the course by discussing the Jawa 8 new features on functional programming
lambda expressions and streams were used more than 200 code examples to illustrate these concepts.
All the code we use is available on our get her repository in 28 minutes.
Jawaid to your question to answer.
What's more you'll also get a free PDA if in the course of contains the questions that we discuss during
these apps as well as a short answer for each one of them.
We have had more than a thousand students do better at their job interview.
Do you want to join them.
Join the cause.
You can also take a test drive by using the free preview feature.
See you in the Indico.